เอาล่ะค่ะทุกท่านขา
มีเรื่องประชาสัมพันธ์นิดนึงนะคะ
ท่านใดที่ทำบัตรจอดรถหล่นหายนะคะ
ติดต่อรับได้ที่จุดแจกของนะคะ
ที่บริเวณชั้น 7 ค่ะ
So anyone of you have lost your parking card,
please contact our souvenir desk.
We have the souvenir desk on the seventh floor.
So please contact the staff over there.
เอาล่ะค่ะ
สำหรับในช่วงถัดไปนี้นะคะ
เราจะเป็น section พิเศษของทาง sponsor ที่น่ารักอีกหนึ่งท่านนะคะ
sponsor ท่านนี้ก็คือ ODDS ค่ะ
ODDS วันนี้เค้าอยากจะฝากข้อความนึงส่งมาให้กับทุกๆ ท่านที่นี่ด้วยนะคะ
ข้อความนั้นมีอยู่ว่า
“ขอให้ทุกท่านสนุกกับงาน conference จาก ODDS
และ ‘We are not hiring’” ค่ะ
โอ้ หัวเราะกันใหญ่เลย
แปลว่าคุ้นเคยกันเป็นอย่างดีอยู่แล้วนะคะ
So this big laugh ladies and gentlemen,
this is because of the special session from ODDS,
one of our beloved sponsor.
And instead of giving a talk,
they would like to give you a short message,
which is “We wish everyone enjoy the conference from ODDS
and ‘We are not hiring.’”
So I hope you enjoy the conference with us here.
Thank you ODDS.